So as you can see we have
arrived in Noida and now we are going for an
interview at ICICI ICI
is the biggest company in India in Lombard okay
and I will pray to God and if you guys
love me then I will crack this interview
and after that I will
start my job from here so for now I am going for the interview,
see you after that how will it be, I will
also show you the inside view
how our
office is
friends you can see how lovely the view of the
office is, how beautifully it is decorated for Holi
you can see
wow hello friends as you saw I have
cracked my job interview okay
in Lombard and then after that I
came here to my Anand Vihar Patparganj to collect
my cheque where I used to work in my first company
I also got my cheque from there
I liked the staff here very much so
friends now I am going towards my home
okay and from here I will take whatever bus or metro I get
and I am quite tired
today after walking the whole day so it felt quite good for
now you should keep giving interviews,
knowledge increases and friends work anywhere you like
Do it with hard work and respect
and give respect and do not take respect, I just
want to say that if you like the video then please
like, comment and subscribe.